The Windblume Festival originated in the "Crown of the North, the City of Freedom"
We gotta bring enough supplies this time, otherwise you'll go hungry again!
So, if you're asking me...
On official business? We're grateful to you
As are we to you
Funny, we haven't gotten together for a meal in a while
It's been so busy lately...
What should we do, on this day?
Mr. Albedo!
How is the research going?
We've had a few issues...
Have a look at this. Now, we think...
Of course, any good tavern offers bar snacks
Really?
How should we do it? Who should we do it for?
Quietly? Or boldly?
Make the first move? Or trust to chance?
Aaaah... Look out!
Sorry, so sorry!
My answer is this:
So long as we can both share fond memories, it doesn't matter
Let the heart decide