Lady Keqing
The item Lady Ningguang prepared for you
Has arrived
Traveler
Wait here for a moment
Don't go anywhere!
Huh? Must be something important!
Traveler
Paimon
Ningguang had her personal tailor
Make it for me
Said it's an imported style
Well?
Do you like it?
Wow, it's beauuutiful!
It's time
Traveler
Please enjoy
The grand finale of this year's Lantern Rite
The Fireworks Show!
Isn't it beautiful?
Whoa...!
Hey, check you out...
Looking pretty fancy!
Only a true treasure catches the eye of Captain Beidou
Seems I've struck gold
With this one
Boo!
Did ya see that?
Way over there, a firework
That looks just like a pig!
Oh?
So it does
Hey everyone, time to eat!
Food's ready!
Ooh!
No better way
To celebrate
Hahaha!
Dr. Baizhu
Sorry to trouble you
Again this year
No trouble at all
Lantern Rite...
Happy Lantern Rite
Happy Lantern Rite!